{
  "decks": [
    {
      "name": "React Router",
      "description": "React Router is a collection of navigational components that compose declaratively with your application.",
      "id": 2
    },
    {
      "name": "New Deck to test 2",
      "description": "sadasd",
      "id": 3
    }
  ],
  "cards": [
    {
      "front": "What path will match the follow Route?\n<Route>\n  <NotFound />\n</Route>",
      "back": "All paths. A route with no path matches all URL's",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 4
    },
    {
      "front": "What does <Switch> do?",
      "back": "Renders the first matching child <Route> ",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 5
    },
    {
      "deckId": null,
      "id": 6
    },
    {
      "front": "What is good?",
      "back": "Soup.",
      "deckId": 3,
      "id": 7
    },
    {
      "front": "Who is good?",
      "back": "You. and me",
      "id": 8
    },
    {
      "front": "Here is another card",
      "back": "Yes No",
      "id": 9
    },
    {
      "front": "and another one",
      "back": "yes yes no",
      "id": 10
    },
    {
      "front": "asda",
      "back": "asdasds",
      "id": 11
    },
    {
      "front": "asdasda",
      "back": "adsasdd",
      "id": 12
    },
    {
      "front": "afdds",
      "back": "asdasdd",
      "id": 13
    },
    {
      "front": "juguzjg",
      "back": "jhbjhbh",
      "id": 14
    },
    {
      "front": "Another Card from ya boi",
      "back": "Boiiiiiiyoooo",
      "id": 15,
      "deckId": 3
    },
    {
      "front": "Card number 3",
      "back": "itsa me",
      "deckId": 3,
      "id": 16
    }
  ]
}